<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Sam Metcalfe&#39;s Analytics Blog</title>
    <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Sam Metcalfe&#39;s Analytics Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://metcalfesports.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gambling for Two Weeks, a cautionary tale.</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2022/05/01/gambling-for-two-weeks-a-cautionary-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2022/05/01/gambling-for-two-weeks-a-cautionary-tale/</guid>
      <description>After ruining March Madness through machine learning (see previous post), I suppose we decided there wasn’t enough negative implications of doing poorly in that challenge. With this in mind, we set out to make millions gambling on NBA basketball. Or at least to try to make millions, and fall devastatingly short.
My team assembled our model based off of the assumption that it was the NBA and no defenses wouyld be played during the duration of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Ruined March Madness in New and Exciting Ways</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2022/04/05/how-i-ruined-march-madness-in-new-and-exciting-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2022/04/05/how-i-ruined-march-madness-in-new-and-exciting-ways/</guid>
      <description>This March, in addition to my usual dumpster fire of a bracket, a new challenger entered the mix. I created a machine learning algorithm to predict each NCAA Tournament game, and used it to fill out a second bracket.
Now between my uncanny intuition and knowledge of the CBB landscape, and a machine built to pick winners from a massive block of numbers, I felt confident that one, if not both of these brackets would be a winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was ACTUALLY the best NBA player of the 2019-2020 NBA Season?</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/24/who-was-actually-the-best-nba-player-of-the-2019-2020-nba-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/24/who-was-actually-the-best-nba-player-of-the-2019-2020-nba-season/</guid>
      <description>The 2019-2020 NBA season was a unique one, with the whole season being put on hold, and then resuming months later in the bubble. This didn’t mean it was any less interesting. The league was flush with stars, both legends like LeBron James, and the emergence of a new generation of superstars, like Luka Dončić.
Giannis Antetokoumnpo, the Greek Freak was crowned as the league’s Most Valuable Player, but was he REALLY the top player in the league last season?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Search For the Greatest QB Season Ever</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/01/the-search-for-the-greatest-qb-season-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/01/the-search-for-the-greatest-qb-season-ever/</guid>
      <description>The Buccaneers winning their championship in 2020 all but put away the debate over who the greatest quarterback of all time is. That’s been settled. I found myself wondering what quarterback season was the greatest ever.
I assembled my list of what I believe to be the top 10 seasons in NFL history. This list was made up of Hall of Famers, Champions, and MVPs. Legends of the sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Post</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/03/15/introductory-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/03/15/introductory-post/</guid>
      <description>This will be the first viewable post of (hopefully) many on this website. The initial purpose of this blog is to store projects for SPMC 350, Sports Analysis and Visualiztion. My hope is that after a while, this domain will serve as a place for me to store projects and writing, whether for a class or not, to be viewed publically and serve as a portfolio. Please Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Sam Metcalfe</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This is my blog I am creating to store my sports analytics projects. I will likely expand it to include papers and other works I feel would be good additions to my portfolio. This is a living project, and will be updated regularly, so feel free to check back in from time to time.
Thank you!
-Sam</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
