<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam Metcalfe&#39;s Analytics Blog</title>
    <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam Metcalfe&#39;s Analytics Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who was ACTUALLY the best NBA player of the 2019-2020 NBA Season?</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/24/who-was-actually-the-best-nba-player-of-the-2019-2020-nba-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/24/who-was-actually-the-best-nba-player-of-the-2019-2020-nba-season/</guid>
      <description>The 2019-2020 NBA season was a unique one, with the whole season being put on hold, and then resuming months later in the bubble. This didn’t mean it was any less interesting. The league was flush with stars, both legends like LeBron James, and the emergence of a new generation of superstars, like Luka Dončić.
Giannis Antetokoumnpo, the Greek Freak was crowned as the league’s Most Valuable Player, but was he REALLY the top player in the league last season?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Search For the Greatest QB Season Ever</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/01/the-search-for-the-greatest-qb-season-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/04/01/the-search-for-the-greatest-qb-season-ever/</guid>
      <description>The Buccaneers winning their championship in 2020 all but put away the debate over who the greatest quarterback of all time is. That’s been settled. I found myself wondering what quarterback season was the greatest ever.
I assembled my list of what I believe to be the top 10 seasons in NFL history. This list was made up of Hall of Famers, Champions, and MVPs. Legends of the sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Post</title>
      <link>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/03/15/introductory-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://metcalfesports.github.io/post/2021/03/15/introductory-post/</guid>
      <description>This will be the first viewable post of (hopefully) many on this website. The initial purpose of this blog is to store projects for SPMC 350, Sports Analysis and Visualiztion. My hope is that after a while, this domain will serve as a place for me to store projects and writing, whether for a class or not, to be viewed publically and serve as a portfolio. Please Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
